So, our goal is to train our neural network.
私たちの目的はニューラルネットワークをトレーニングすることです
In order to do this,
そのためには
we have to define the error function.
エラー関数を定義する必要があります
So, let's look again at what the error function was for perceptrons.
それではパーセプトロンにとってエラー関数とは何かをもう一度見てみましょう
So, here's our perceptron.
これがパーセプトロンです
In the left, we have our input vector with
左には入力ベクターがあり
entries x_1 up to x_n, and one for the bias unit.
エントリーx1からxnまでとバイアスユニットとしての1があります
And the edges with weights W_1 up to W_n,
エッジには重みW1からWnまでと
and b for the bias unit.
バイアスユニットとしてbがあります
Finally, we can see that this perceptor uses a sigmoid function.
最後に このパーセプトロンはシグモイド関数を使用していることがわかります
And the prediction is defined as y-hat equals sigmoid of Wx plus b.
予測はyハット＝シグモイド(Wx+b)として定義されます
And as we saw, this function gives us a measure of
見てのとおり この関数は
the error of how badly each point is being classified.
各ポイントがどのように誤って分類されているかというエラーの尺度を与えてくれます
Roughly, this is a very small number if the point is correctly classified,
大まかに言って ポイントが正しく分類されている場合 これは非常に小さい数であり
and a measure of how far the point is from
直線からのポイントの距離は
the line and the point is incorrectly classified.
ポイントが誤って分類されているときの測定になります
So, what are we going to do to define the error function in a multilayer perceptron?
では 多層パーセプトロンでエラー関数を定義するにはどうしたらよいでしょうか
Well, as we saw, our prediction is simply
見てのとおり 予測は
a combination of matrix multiplications and sigmoid functions.
行列乗算とシグモイド関数の組み合わせにすぎません
But the error function can be the exact same thing, right?
しかし エラー関数は正確に同じものでしょうか
It can be the exact same formula,
まったく同じ式になりえますが
except now, y-hat is just a bit more complicated.
yハットは少しだけ複雑です
And still, this function will tell us how badly a point gets misclassified.
やはり この関数はポイントがどれくらい誤って分類されているかを示します
Except now, it's looking at a more complicated boundary.
ただし 境界がより複雑です